<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eda on Data Science Explorer</title>
    <link>/tags/eda/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Eda on Data Science Explorer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/eda/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The games I played in 2018 Part One - EDA</title>
      <link>/post/the-games-i-played-in-2018-part-one-eda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-games-i-played-in-2018-part-one-eda/</guid>
      <description># TODO - add lat and long details of gaming locations # TODO - group games by RPG, digital and board # TODO - add weekday names and weekend/weekday categories # TODO - add morning/afternoon/evening categories  In 2018 I decided to track every game I played using the BG Stats app. The app comes with some built in statistics which are useful but don’t answer all my questions.
Today I’m going to do some exploratory work in R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EDA with R and PostgreSQL</title>
      <link>/post/eda-with-r-and-postgresql/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/eda-with-r-and-postgresql/</guid>
      <description>Today I connect my R session to a PostgreSQL database.
I’m using the tutorial database of DVD rentals and this.
My objectives are to;
 learn how to connect R to a database
 practice using SQL queries within R Markdown
 uncover material to use in the SQL project for the Udacity Programming For Data Science Nanodegree  library(tidyverse) library(here) library(ggthemes) library(RPostgreSQL) drv &amp;lt;- dbDriver(&amp;quot;PostgreSQL&amp;quot;) con &amp;lt;- dbConnect(drv, dbname = &amp;quot;dvdrental&amp;quot;, host = &amp;quot;localhost&amp;quot;, port = 5432, user = &amp;quot;postgres&amp;quot;, password = pw) Exploring the database There are 15 tables in this relational database, connected as follows;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Hour EDA - fitzRoy R Package</title>
      <link>/post/one-hour-eda-fitzroy-r-package/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/one-hour-eda-fitzroy-r-package/</guid>
      <description>Today I take a closer look at the info available in the fitzRoy package.
 This is such a great example of what is happening in the R community these days, the package really takes away the difficulty out of scraping the web for data.
I will limit myself to one hour. This will cover all the poking and prodding of the data and the writing and editing of this post.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>