<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Before the Game on Summoner Of Games</title>
    <link>/tags/before-the-game/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Before the Game on Summoner Of Games</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/before-the-game/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyborian Arena 0</title>
      <link>/games_reports/hyborian-arena-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/games_reports/hyborian-arena-0/</guid>
      <description>Slaves and prisoners of war from across the lands are brought to this brutal arena where they are tested in mortal combat.
The Hyborian Arena is a place to teach the basics of combat in the Conan 2d20 system. To prepare you should;
 Create a character Create a Roll20 account  Some of the features include;
 Arena map from classic Conan tile set Rule references from core rule book Doom and Momentum counters  Although designed as a tutorial for single sessions, there is also a campaign element to this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conan Adventures in Hot Springs Island 0</title>
      <link>/games_reports/conan-adventures-in-hot-springs-island-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/games_reports/conan-adventures-in-hot-springs-island-0/</guid>
      <description>I am excited to try out the Conan Adventures in An Age Undreamed Of RPG. It looks like a really well-designed system, oozing with Doom, Momentum and primal flavour.
As well, I am intrigued by the Hot Springs Island products. These define a system-neutral hex-crawling sandbox, set on a jungle island with two volcanoes.
Putting these two together seems like the greatest combination since ice-cream and chocolate sauce.
The setting I place Hot Springs Island in Hyboria, specifically as one of the tropical islands near Argos and Zingara where pirates ply their trade.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>