<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Summoner Of Games</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Summoner Of Games</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XXIX</title>
      <link>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xxix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xxix/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XXVIII</title>
      <link>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xxviii/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xxviii/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XXVII</title>
      <link>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xxvii/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xxvii/</guid>
      <description>The 27th episode of Out Of The Abyss ended with us victoriously returning to Blingdenstone.
Killed. Raised. Interrogated.
 The King Of The Dead Pudding King “This is my tiger” says the chipper halfling who lounges easily at the bar in The Foaming Mug.
Salazar is not so sure, but is diplomatic as always.
“Remarkable… your tiger must be rare indeed, one could be mistaken for believing it is a house-cat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XXVI</title>
      <link>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xxvi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xxvi/</guid>
      <description>Exciting things happened  DM/Designer Notes I missed the 26th session of Out Of The Abyss. Our group deals with this pretty easily, we abstract away the fact a character was not present. The Underdark is a crazy place, people come and go, die, go insane, turn to stone.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XXV</title>
      <link>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xxv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xxv/</guid>
      <description>The 25th episode of Out Of The Abyss ended with us at the end of a trap-filled corridor.
We keep running into these
 Eldritch Knights, Battle Masters, Were-rats and Oozes “Bryson Hardcastle, Commissioned Adventurer” says the half-elf by way of introduction, extending a gloved hand and delivering a handshake that is supple yet strong and wholly professional. “Now, what kind of trouble have you gotten yourselves into?”
“I am Salazar and these are my companions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XXIV</title>
      <link>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xxiv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xxiv/</guid>
      <description>The 24th episode of Out Of The Abyss ended with us most of us escaping a medusa after defeating a lich.
Undead Mind Flayer. Now I’m really scared.
 There must be something nearby that can turn people to stone… The stone structure seems timeless, an ancient an holy site where gnomes have worshipped their gods of stone and earth…until recently. A foulness lies about the air, and as the holy ruby is clicked into place, you hear the keen wailing of the undead approaching…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XXIII</title>
      <link>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xxiii/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xxiii/</guid>
      <description>The 23rd episode of Out Of The Abyss ended with us barely alive in search of a sunken temple.
I am scared. Scared to death.
 Forbidden knowledge “I don’t like the look of that Jimjar fellow…” says Gadreel as she watches Lyssiwick walk up the stairs with the rakish gnome adventurer. “Don’t worry, I have a plan” says the gnomish wizard, “this is all for the Greater Good”.
———</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XXII</title>
      <link>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xxii/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xxii/</guid>
      <description>The 22nd episode of Out Of The Abyss ended with us inside the city of Blingdenstone.
Worth at least 5000gp
 The tests of Plates, Cups and Forks Tredrea approaches the defeated Cave Badger, which lies barely breathing on the smooth stone floor. “The Bitch Queen has not called you yet” he says, kneeling to tend to the animal’s wounds and restore it to consciousness. “I will never understand you” says Salazar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dawn Of Worlds</title>
      <link>/post/dawn-of-worlds/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/dawn-of-worlds/</guid>
      <description>At the London Indie RPG Meetup we played Dawn Of Worlds; a collaborative game where the players co-create an epic fantasy world. It was an interesting, fun, somewhat hilarious experience, here is the result…
An un-named world of extreme adventure.
 Mighty events that shaped our world From the jagged-toothed maw of un-knowable depths, a pillar of Eternal Flame rises!
A great serpent is seen moving through the whirlpool ridden seas, thirsting for the riches of the deeps!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XXI</title>
      <link>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xxi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xxi/</guid>
      <description>The 21st episode of Out Of The Abyss ended with us trapped inside a trap-filled corridor.
Do you run away?
 There must be something valuable at the end of this trap-filled corridor “Come closer child of fire, and let the power of the Wavemother heal thy wounds.” Tredrea slowly traces the words carved into the ancient stone tablet. Although he cannot read, even in his own language, he knows deeply that there is magic here that can restore Gadreel, the mysterious tiefling ranger of the Underdark, from her grievous wounds suffered at the hands of demons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyborian Arena 0</title>
      <link>/post/hyborian-arena-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hyborian-arena-0/</guid>
      <description>Slaves and prisoners of war from across the lands are brought to this brutal arena where they are tested in mortal combat.
The Hyborian Arena is a place to teach the basics of combat in the Conan 2d20 system. To prepare you should;
 Create a character Create a Roll20 account  Some of the features include;
 Arena map from classic Conan tile set Rule references from core rule book Doom and Momentum counters  Although designed as a tutorial for single sessions, there is also a campaign element to this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XX</title>
      <link>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xx/</guid>
      <description>The 20th episode of Out Of The Abyss ended with us outside the gates to a strange underground city, home to the mysterious Deep Gnomes…
Blingdenstone (art by BryanSyme on DeviantArt).
 Salazar’s Fungal Grotto Of Delights Vampiric Death “I proclaim this island in the name of Basidia and our Myconid friends”, proclaims Salazar The Bard, his words echoing musically through the caverns that envelope the tributaries that feed Darklake. “What about the devilfish?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conan Adventures in Hot Springs Island 0</title>
      <link>/post/conan-adventures-in-hot-springs-island-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/conan-adventures-in-hot-springs-island-0/</guid>
      <description>I am excited to try out the Conan Adventures in An Age Undreamed Of RPG. It looks like a really well-designed system, oozing with Doom, Momentum and primal flavour.
As well, I am intrigued by the Hot Springs Island products. These define a system-neutral hex-crawling sandbox, set on a jungle island with two volcanoes.
Putting these two together seems like the greatest combination since ice-cream and chocolate sauce.
The setting I place Hot Springs Island in Hyboria, specifically as one of the tropical islands near Argos and Zingara where pirates ply their trade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slowplay - an approach to learning and playing RPGs</title>
      <link>/post/slowplay-an-approach-to-learning-relaxing-and-writing-with-tabletop-rpgs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/slowplay-an-approach-to-learning-relaxing-and-writing-with-tabletop-rpgs/</guid>
      <description>It has been mentioned many times that RPG enthusiasts will often spend much more time reading about games than actually playing them. This is certainly true for me, evidenced by the ever-growing collection of games I have, coupled with the ever-decreasing amount of time I am able to co-ordinate to run or play them.
I also have a parallel interest in game design. So when I am reading an RPG product, my daydreaming is going in a few different directions; what would it be like to play this game, what would it be like to run this game, and how was it designed?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XIX</title>
      <link>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/out-of-the-abyss-xix/</guid>
      <description>I am lucky to play in an excellent face-to-face campaign run by Edward from the London Dungeons and Dragons Meetup.
There have been 18 sessions so far, following the Out Of The Abyss campaign for 5th Edition Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons. Edward keeps great notes and so do some of the players, so I will add elements of these in future.
For now, prepare to hear a few dread tales of The Underdark as experienced from the viewpoint of Tredrea Meksoith, Pirate King Of Darklake and True Servant Of The Bitch Queen…</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>