<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>After the Game on Summoner Of Games</title>
    <link>/tags/after-the-game/</link>
    <description>Recent content in After the Game on Summoner Of Games</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/after-the-game/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tales From The Loop II</title>
      <link>/games_reports/tales-from-the-loop-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/games_reports/tales-from-the-loop-ii/</guid>
      <description>The adults are disappearing…and that’s a bad thing? The kids wake up and decide to drive to Stenhamra to access the library and try to find out about the ship IEX-4Z32. Ylva knows how to break in there, it’s easy. Not so easy is figuring out if the car has enough petrol to get them there and back. They may need to refuel at one of the robotic stations which will surely require some sort of ID.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tales From The Loop I</title>
      <link>/games_reports/tales-from-the-loop-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/games_reports/tales-from-the-loop-i/</guid>
      <description>The kids took this bus before deciding to borrow a car.
 Our parents will kill us if we are killed by killer birds Summer holidays on the Malaren Islands. The kids meet as usual in the boarded-up, closed-down community library in Kungsberga.
There’s Kristine, the most popular girl in school, according to reputable sources such as herself. She looks at herself in the mirror placed against one wall and tries not to think about her crazy aunt in the basement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XXIX</title>
      <link>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xxix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xxix/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XXVIII</title>
      <link>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xxviii/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xxviii/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XXVII</title>
      <link>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xxvii/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xxvii/</guid>
      <description>The 27th episode of Out Of The Abyss ended with us victoriously returning to Blingdenstone.
Killed. Raised. Interrogated.
 The King Of The Dead Pudding King “This is my tiger” says the chipper halfling who lounges easily at the bar in The Foaming Mug.
Salazar is not so sure, but is diplomatic as always.
“Remarkable… your tiger must be rare indeed, one could be mistaken for believing it is a house-cat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XXVI</title>
      <link>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xxvi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xxvi/</guid>
      <description>Exciting things happened  DM/Designer Notes I missed the 26th session of Out Of The Abyss. Our group deals with this pretty easily, we abstract away the fact a character was not present. The Underdark is a crazy place, people come and go, die, go insane, turn to stone.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XXV</title>
      <link>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xxv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xxv/</guid>
      <description>The 25th episode of Out Of The Abyss ended with us at the end of a trap-filled corridor.
We keep running into these
 Eldritch Knights, Battle Masters, Were-rats and Oozes “Bryson Hardcastle, Commissioned Adventurer” says the half-elf by way of introduction, extending a gloved hand and delivering a handshake that is supple yet strong and wholly professional. “Now, what kind of trouble have you gotten yourselves into?”
“I am Salazar and these are my companions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XXIV</title>
      <link>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xxiv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xxiv/</guid>
      <description>The 24th episode of Out Of The Abyss ended with us most of us escaping a medusa after defeating a lich.
Undead Mind Flayer. Now I’m really scared.
 There must be something nearby that can turn people to stone… The stone structure seems timeless, an ancient an holy site where gnomes have worshipped their gods of stone and earth…until recently. A foulness lies about the air, and as the holy ruby is clicked into place, you hear the keen wailing of the undead approaching…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XXIII</title>
      <link>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xxiii/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xxiii/</guid>
      <description>The 23rd episode of Out Of The Abyss ended with us barely alive in search of a sunken temple.
I am scared. Scared to death.
 Forbidden knowledge “I don’t like the look of that Jimjar fellow…” says Gadreel as she watches Lyssiwick walk up the stairs with the rakish gnome adventurer. “Don’t worry, I have a plan” says the gnomish wizard, “this is all for the Greater Good”.
———</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XXII</title>
      <link>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xxii/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xxii/</guid>
      <description>The 22nd episode of Out Of The Abyss ended with us inside the city of Blingdenstone.
Worth at least 5000gp
 The tests of Plates, Cups and Forks Tredrea approaches the defeated Cave Badger, which lies barely breathing on the smooth stone floor. “The Bitch Queen has not called you yet” he says, kneeling to tend to the animal’s wounds and restore it to consciousness. “I will never understand you” says Salazar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dawn Of Worlds</title>
      <link>/games_reports/dawn-of-worlds/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/games_reports/dawn-of-worlds/</guid>
      <description>At the London Indie RPG Meetup we played Dawn Of Worlds; a collaborative game where the players co-create an epic fantasy world. It was an interesting, fun, somewhat hilarious experience, here is the result…
An un-named world of extreme adventure.
 Mighty events that shaped our world From the jagged-toothed maw of un-knowable depths, a pillar of Eternal Flame rises!
A great serpent is seen moving through the whirlpool ridden seas, thirsting for the riches of the deeps!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XXI</title>
      <link>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xxi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xxi/</guid>
      <description>The 21st episode of Out Of The Abyss ended with us trapped inside a trap-filled corridor.
Do you run away?
 There must be something valuable at the end of this trap-filled corridor “Come closer child of fire, and let the power of the Wavemother heal thy wounds.” Tredrea slowly traces the words carved into the ancient stone tablet. Although he cannot read, even in his own language, he knows deeply that there is magic here that can restore Gadreel, the mysterious tiefling ranger of the Underdark, from her grievous wounds suffered at the hands of demons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XX</title>
      <link>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xx/</guid>
      <description>The 20th episode of Out Of The Abyss ended with us outside the gates to a strange underground city, home to the mysterious Deep Gnomes…
Blingdenstone (art by BryanSyme on DeviantArt).
 Salazar’s Fungal Grotto Of Delights Vampiric Death “I proclaim this island in the name of Basidia and our Myconid friends”, proclaims Salazar The Bard, his words echoing musically through the caverns that envelope the tributaries that feed Darklake. “What about the devilfish?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of The Abyss XIX</title>
      <link>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/games_reports/out-of-the-abyss-xix/</guid>
      <description>I am lucky to play in an excellent face-to-face campaign run by Edward from the London Dungeons and Dragons Meetup.
There have been 18 sessions so far, following the Out Of The Abyss campaign for 5th Edition Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons. Edward keeps great notes and so do some of the players, so I will add elements of these in future.
For now, prepare to hear a few dread tales of The Underdark as experienced from the viewpoint of Tredrea Meksoith, Pirate King Of Darklake and True Servant Of The Bitch Queen…</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>